mayura4ever.com 2017-11-17

# Privacy Policy

At Mayura4Ever, I appreciate your readership and loyalty. With respect I value your privacy at first place. So it's my responsibility to let you know what information being gathered and purposes of collecting them, to create a transparent relationship with you as a valued reader.

This "Privacy Policy" may update at any time and you can check back at any time to ensure that you are familiar with most recent version of our Privacy Policy. 

###  HOW: You Provide Your Personal Information?

i. By sharing your e-mail address when subscribing to the newsletter

ii. By sharing your email address when contacting me through the contact form

iii. By sharing personal information when you post comments / support requests

In addition to your basic information, web analytic trackers, third-party services and advertising partners may collect other information such as country origin, your internet browser and operating system used to surf Mayura4Ever.

The advertisements appears on Mayura4Ever, served by third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this weblog. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to this blog and / or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/) too.

Apart from advertisers, other trackers and services will use cookies to improve quality of their service too. If you wish to disable cookies, you may go through your web browser options. "Mayura4Ever" itself has no access or control over any of those cookies.

###  HOW: I Use Your Personal Information

I do use web analytic data to track site traffic, analyze statistics and identify trends to deliver better user experience for you. In addition, here's how I might use your personal information.

i. The email address you provide by subscribing to the newsletter, enable me to send you latest updates of this weblog. You can find unsubscribe link to opt-out from the newsletters at any time and I don't use your email address for any other purposes such as promotions. However, I might use it to convey any vital update relates to email subscription service that I think you should know as a subscriber.

ii. The email address you provide through the contact form will not be shared with anyone else or use for any other purposes. The only purpose is responding to your inquiry.

iii. The personal information you provide through commenting on blog posts will not be used for any purposes. But I may use it to contact you if you have been violating any of guidelines when you interact with the community on this weblog.

This weblog is powered by Blogger and third party services may also collect your non-personal information for their purposes. You can read their privacy policies to be familiar with what they have been collecting.

AddThis Privacy Policy <http://www.addthis.com/privacy>

Disqus Privacy Policy: <http://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy>

If you have any inquiries about this Privacy Policy, please [contact me](http://www.mayura4ever.com/p/contact.html) with your inquiry detailing relevant information. I appreciate any of your considerations.

**Last Updated** : 2014 November 27
